Approved.
Chef from South Park.
It's genius.
Just some chef.
I've decided to pre-screen
all of the Halloween
costumes this year.
I have three simple rules,
don't be offensive,
don't be cliché
and don't take
the first two rules
too seriously.
The gorilla from
Rise of the Planet
of the Apes.
Huh?
The one who
sacrifices his life.
Whoa! Oh.
Spoiler alert.
It's been out
for ages, man.
Costume vetoed.
Uh...
It's... Somebody's
already called that.
Who?
Kevin has a gorilla suit
you could borrow.
This is ridiculous!
Why can't there just be
two Kate Middletons?
Guys, I know,
I mean I wish
there could be too.
It's like I can't choose.
They're both
amazing, it's just...
Look, I stayed up all night
and I watched
that G.D. wedding
and then I came to work
and I made everyone
else watch it all day.
Meredith wasn't even here.
Because I was there.
MEREDITH: (ON VIDEO)
You're the people's princess!
Diana was nothing!
I thought you were
at your sister's funeral.
What I said was,
"My sister's funeral
is this weekend."
Didn't say
I'd be there.
Why is it such a shock
that I follow the royal story?
Warms my heart,
thinking about
them two kids...
...doing it.
Can I maybe
squeeze through?
Here you go.
There we go. Thank you.
ERIN: When they talk about
all the nice things
about dating a co-worker,
they don't mention
one of the best parts.
After you're done dating,
you still get to work
together every single day.
Jim, put it on.
DARRYL: Put it on, man.
I don't know if I can.
Come on,
the Three Amigos.
Three Kings.
All right.
JIM: I know, I know, I know.
But Darryl and Kevin
needed a third.
They bought me
this jersey. I said no.
Kevin started crying, so
I am Chris Bosh.
RYAN: If you get
into season one,
you know, really...
Oh, my God, what the hell
is wrong with you?
It's called a costume.
What are you?
Some kind of
Jamaican zombie woman?
Ryan, will you please
tell her who I am?
Whoopi Goldberg.
Has no one here heard
of Kerrigan, from StarCraft?
Queen of blades.
It's all Toby's fault.
Every Halloween,
I tell him the same thing.
You can't bring weapons
into the office.
And every year he says
the same thing.
"As soon as I get
my weapons back,
I'm going to kill you."
But there I am
at Thanksgiving alive,
you know?
I'm a lucky turkey.
Everybody looking good?
This is the best we can do?
I'm not judging.
I think you guys
look great, I just...
...want to make sure
this is the best
we can do.
I just got a text
from Broccoli Rob. "Boo!"
It scared me.
And then I got this text
from Robert California.
"Looking forward
to Halloween party.
Expectations are high."
Scared the (BLEEP)
out of me.
G'day, Pameroo.
Could you shoot
this off for me?
Yeah.
Australian accent.
What are you doing?
I just wanted to see
how you do it.
If you're doing
something I don't.
Are you...
That Andy,
so hot and cold.
One day he's like,
"Fax these documents, please."
The next he's like, "Pam,
you fax them. Who cares
what Erin's feeling." Right?
Oh, Erin.
Pam,
how would you rate me
as a receptionist on
a scale of one to three?
Um.
Two?
It's like the second
to last thing
I wanted to hear.
No, I mean
you're doing great
and Andy put you
in charge of
the whole party, right?
Yeah.
Send completed.
You are the best
in the biz. I can't deny.
Bob and I are doing
this Scranton haunted
walking tour.
I always wondered
what kind of people
went on that thing.
Hey, if you go
by the Banshee Pub,
tell the Man in Black
I say hello.
What happened, Pam?
Okay.
When I was 22, I worked there
and everybody said
the place was haunted.
I didn't believe it
until one day,
before we opened,
I look up into the mirror,
you know, behind the bar?
And I see this old man
dressed all in black,
but when I turn around,
there's no one there.
So, I tell the cook
my story...
Wait, they have food there?
...and he said,
"That's what everyone sees.
That's the Man in Black."
No. My wife does not
believe in ghosts.
Hey.
Oh.
This Man in Black thing.
What do you think
that was about?
What do you mean?
Was it like trickery
in the lights
or maybe you were
so primed to see it,
then there it was.
I saw a ghost.
Mm-hmm.
What I'm saying is, like,
do you ever wonder
what it was?
It was a ghost.
I told you this on
like our first date.
Yeah, I had just told you
about the day that I met
the Blue Angels.
I figured you had to top it.
I don't know what
to tell you, Jim,
but I saw a ghost.
Hey!
Uh-oh.
Looks like we're under
a Jack attack.
ROBERT: Yes, Andrew.
And you, on this
day of fantasy,
are a laborer.
Yes.
Everyone, this is
Bert, my son.
Bert, this is
a paper company.
ALL: Hey, Bert!
Hello.
Can I use a computer?
I need to check a hurricane.
Here, use this one.
All right.
Oh, look, pin the word
on the witch.
How did you know
I was bringing my son?
I didn't. It was for us.
But he can play.
Berty Boy, would you
like to play this game?
That stuff's for babies.
Perhaps this party
will awaken
the baby in all of us.
Wow. Who shot
our grownup party
with the kiddy ray gun?
We're still getting it set up.
It's going to be really cool.
(CHUCKLING)
Extraordinary.
Did you plan this?
Well, Toby and I did, yeah.
And I overheard and thought,
"Hey, that'd be fun,
don't mind if I do."
If you turn out the lights,
we'll do a little dance.
KELLY: One, two, three.
(ALL SINGING)
Dem bones, dem bones,
dem dry bones
Now we're the skeleton crew
Delightful.
Thank you.
Now then,
how are we today?
Fine.
Great.
Just fine, Kelly?
Everything all right?
Mm-hmm.
You feeling fulfilled
in your life?
I guess.
You guess?
So there is something
you want that you
do not have.
Try not to think
about it.
Because it's too
terrifying to imagine.
Now we're cooking.
What is it, Kelly?
What is this great
fear of yours?
Never marrying.
Yes. Dying alone,
that is very scary.
And how are you, Toby?
So great.
Oh, I put those up.
I know. I'm taking
them down.
I almost wonder
if putting nothing
on this wall
is more Halloween-y.
I don't know
about this, guys.
Andy put me in charge of
the Halloween party, so.
Well, Andy sent us
in here, so which is it?
Oh.
So can we speak our
minds now? Or are we still
sparing feelings?
Because I hate
all of this.
Very low pressure
in the Sargasso Sea.
Warm air from South America.
Cold air from Greenland.
All signs point
to the perfect storm.
Perfectly mediocre.
What are you, anyway?
I'm a Jamaican zombie woman.
Leave me alone, ghoul.
If you had some
really big wings
with blades on the end,
you'd kind of look
like Kerrigan
from StarCraft.
Damn it! I am Kerrigan
I've been censored.
If you're going
to be a Zerg,
at least be a lurker.
Not some girl.
Kerrigan is ruler
of the Zerg swarm.
Yeah. She also has boobs.
Yeah, but no nipples.
Hey.
Hey, what's up?
November's sure
creeping up, ain't it?
You can't stop that month.
Hey, what's the jive with
Angela and Phyllis helping
with the party, you know?
Um...
I just thought
you could use
some help, you know?
'Cause Robert came in
and thought the party
seemed a little kiddy.
And I guess I agreed.
And maybe we could
mix a little more 13
into the PG.
But that's it?
There's nothing
about me or I?
Can we talk about it
at the end of the day?
I got a call.
I got to make a call.
Yeah, sorry.
Yes, we can.
Yes. I don't know.
Mm-hmm.
Gabe?
Sweet Erin.
I'm throwing the Halloween
party and I just want
to amp it up a little.
I think it could use
some extra pizzazz.
Okay. Where does
Gabe factor in?
Remember that
Halloween party
you took me to once?
The one where I started crying
as soon as I walked in
and I didn't stop crying?
Yes. Lars and Takako's.
Okay, well let's say
that I wanted this party
to be a tiny,
tiny bit like that one,
just more adult,
more scary and sexy.
I will make this sexier
than you could ever imagine.
No, just scary.
If we wanted
ideas for scary stuff.
(CHUCKLING)
No, that'd be scary.
What are you thinking about?
All right, let me go get it.
(PHONE RINGING)
Pam Halpert.
Hey. It's Jim Halpert.
I was wondering if you
wanted to see
a movie tonight
'cause I've read a lot about
this really great documentary.
Is it called Ghostbusters?
It's called Ghostbusters.
It didn't look like that.
He didn't have
a buster sign around him?
Why don't you draw him?
Why don't we see
this old man?
Okay. Yeah.
Fine, I'll draw him.
Okay.
I ain't afraid of no ghosts.
Whoa.
Mm-hmm.
Dwight, are you
eating a stick?
It's a root, idiot.
Okay.
Everyone hates you.
That's really rude.
I don't tell you
hurricanes suck
even though it's true.
What do you like,
tornadoes?
Try influenza.
Yeah? What's the vaccine
you could take
to avoid a hurricane?
Open up a newspaper.
Look, a hurricane's coming.
I suppose you're going
to tell me the scariest
animal is a shark.
Try box jellyfish.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
What are we talking about?
I was talking about
my wife and how
she believes in ghosts.
Then we had a little debate
and then Meredith said
that she believes in them too.
You seem unimpressed.
Ghosts don't scare you?
I'm only scared
of real things, like serial
killers and kidnappers.
Not things that don't exist
like ghosts or mummies.
Mummies are real.
There are mummies
at museums.
Yeah.
You prank.
It's true. They've
been preserved for
thousands of years.
They're all over.
Why on Earth
would a museum
put a mummy in it?
ERIN: A little
witch's brew?
I grew this party
up real fast.
Get out of here,
little kid party.
Nobody loves you.
And clean up your room!
Grownups are going
to use it later.
The party looks fun,
doesn't it?
Everybody seems
to be in there
having a great time.
So maybe now would be
a great time for me
to pop back on the computer.
I'm using it.
I'm about to play
StarCraft with him.
You serious?
Yeah, I'm serious.
Hey, hey. That's funny.
Okay.
Loser.
Pam, do you think anyone's
going to notice I've worn
this costume before
when I wasn't pregnant?
You know,
I guess nobody would
believe it still fits.
Hey, guys, I'm
an Oscar Liar Weiner.
Oh, my God.
Party's tight, E.
Fog is cool.
Thanks.
It's on medium.
Perfect.
It really looks great.
You did a great job.
Oh. So we don't have
to have that talk?
We should still
have that talk.
Maybe you could
come by my office
at like 4:45?
Cool.
Okay.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(IN SPOOKY VOICE)
Okay, everybody,
be prepared
to be scared.
Okay.
GABE: The Cinema
of the Unsettling
is a growing film movement.
The most well known
film in the genre
is an hour long shot
of a squirrel
with diarrhea.
(ALL REACTING WITH DISGUST)
Okay. Ew.
Is that my grandmother?
What's the story?
OSCAR: There is no story.
GABE: Yeah, seems like
there isn't a narrative.
Maybe the filmmaker realized
that even narrative
is comforting.
STANLEY: What the hell
is going on here?
Okay, I think
we've seen enough.
You can turn it off now.
ALL: Yeah.
Yeah, kill it. Go ahead
and turn it off.
Thank you.
STANLEY: How'd you
get in my car?
Where is this from?
That is so upsetting.
That was awful.
Robert, I apologize.
I'm sorry. I got confused.
I heard that you
wanted to make the party
more adult but,
I think I know what to do now.
This game is called
"Pecker Poker."
(ALL GROANING)
It's the game of cards
that gets you hard.
What we have here
is a classic
misunderstanding.
Why didn't you simply
ask Andy to clarify?
Asking is a very
easy thing to do.
The two of you are
obviously very close.
Oh, I see. This no longer
seems like my business.
All I knew is that
you wanted to have
a talk with me
at the end of the day
and I got nervous, so...
You were going
to talk at the end of...
I'm not here.
Did you think I was
going to fire you?
No, I wasn't.
I'm sorry.
This must be really
uncomfortable for you.
I'm never uncomfortable.
Okay.
Erin, I think you know
I've been dating someone.
Sure.
And it's getting
a little more serious.
She's never come by, so.
And she's never called here.
Unless it's your mom.
No, I didn't want her
to call because I thought
it would be weird, but,
now it's weird
that she's not calling.
Two dates?
Three dates?
Thirty-one.
Wow.
I'm so happy
for you guys.
Um. Let me know
when you get to 40.
I'll see you guys.
I should go.
I just don't get it, Pam.
I mean, you're
a rational person.
Thank you.
Jim doesn't let me wash
his NFL jersey
during the playoffs.
How is this
any less logical?
Careful. Whoa.
First of all, it's not like
I think that's going
to help the Eagles win.
Really?
No.
That is just a bunch
of people participating
in a collective thing.
And maybe the Eagles
will hear about it and want
to play better. It's not...
Exactly.
Thank you.
Go! Get up there
right now.
Got it.
Dwight.
You want to attack,
or let them come to us?
Your call, B.
Unleash the hell storm.
DARRYL: Dwight.
Nice.
Dwight.
Got 'em. Go!
Is she Asian?
I don't know. She's
from somewhere, I bet.
Maybe from the forest.
Forest?
Did Andy say his girlfriend's
from the forest?
I don't know, Phyllis.
Maybe she's from the city.
Looks terribly real,
doesn't it, Creed?
No.
Are you scared of snakes?
You don't live
as long as I have
without a healthy fear
of snakes, Bobby.
Yeah, I guess sometimes
I have nightmares
about being buried alive.
Honestly, Jim gives
me the creeps.
What am I up to?
Like a few years
down the road, Cece says,
"Mom, there's
a ghost in my closet."
Now you say one of two things.
One, "You're just having
a bad dream."
Or two, "Let's go see
what it wants."
I'm not going
to freak her out, Jim.
Okay.
I'm not going to lie
to her either.
Oh, come on.
When I was a boy,
there was an empty house,
just up the hill
from my family's.
It was rumored
a man committed
suicide there
after being possessed
by the devil.
One day, a young woman, Lydia,
moved into the house
with her infant child.
That very night Lydia
was awakened by a loud,
heinous hissing sound.
(HISSING)
She walked to the nursery
and there in baby's
crib was a snake
wrapped around baby's neck,
squeezing tighter and tighter.
Oh, my goodness.
The crib was full of dirt,
baby struggled
to free itself
from underneath,
reaching and clawing,
gasping for air.
Embalmed bodies rose
from their sarcophagi,
lurching toward baby.
For they were mummies.
No.
Amongst them was a man.
Tall, slim.
Jim.
Almost instinctively
she turned to her husband.
"Wait," she thought,
"I don't have a husband."
For Lydia and her husband had
had an argument,
one they couldn't get past.
Each night they slept
one inch farther apart
until one night Lydia left.
It was about this time
she lost herself
in imaginary worlds.
She had quit
the book club,
the choir,
citing something about
their high expectations.
Her lips slowly
grew together from disuse.
Every time she wanted
to act, and didn't,
another part of her face
hardened until it was stone.
And that fevered night,
she rushed to the nursery,
and threw open the door.
"Baby, are you okay?"
Baby sat up slowly,
turned to mother
and said,
"I'm fine, bitch. I'm fine."
(LAUGHING)
Fear plays an interesting
role in our lives.
How dare we let
it motivate us?
How dare we let it
into our decision making?
Into our livelihoods.
Into our relationships.
It's funny, isn't it? We take
a day a year to dress up
in costume and celebrate fear.
Toby.
Hey, Bert. Want
to see the dance?
Dem bones,
dem bones, dem dry...
You're fired.
What?
You heard me.
Pack your things.
What? You can't...
Gabe? Are you...
I'm the CEO's son.
Pack your things.
You're done.